[{"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "I mean, when a candidate starts telling supporters it's time for a reassessment, it's over, isn't it?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Piers, I'm not 100 percent confident that when I walk out of this building that, I'm not going to get struck by lightning.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Are you 100 percent confident, you, his close friend, his adviser, are you 100 percent confident that she is simply inventing a 13-year affair?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "You know, I have no way of knowing who to believe in all of this.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Who do you believe?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "But are you really going to look the American public in the eye collectively as a team and say, every one of these women is a fantasist?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "I mean, why wouldn't his lawyer say the same thing he's saying?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "I would advise that that is a blow that would be difficult to come back from.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "If it turns out Herman Cain has been telling porky pies and has had an affair with this woman, would you then advise him to stand down?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "You know, I just think that -- Mark.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Why, Michael?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "He needed to do the documentary.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Isn't that going to be antagonistic?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I just got to say this.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Do you accept that?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Will you appeal?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Well, the judge might assess restitution in the sum of $100 million in January when we have to go back to court.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Does Conrad Murray have any money?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Today, yes, I have been expecting the worst ever since the jury said guilty.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Were you expecting the worst of it?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I haven't talked with him today.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "And how is Conrad today?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I think that they have to know that somewhere along the way that the whole thing's going to go off the rails.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "I mean, are there many doctors in Hollywood that would ever do that to somebody of Michael Jackson's stature?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "I think it's appalling.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, I have to say Elizabeth Smart.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Of all these cases, John, which is the one that has the most significance to you personally?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Piers, that's the introduction I wish I had every time I went home right there.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Dane, how are you?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I'm about 1.5.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "What are you at?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "We're fragile souls, Piers.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Isn't that true about comedians?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "So why be on a medium where a load of people come on every day and say you are not funny?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "That's true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, yeah.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "It's the ultimate kind of thing that you crave, isn't it?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Oh, wow.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "How many have you literally laughed into bed?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Not as many as you.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "How about you?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "You can't leave it at four, because you need a football team, with at least five a side.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Is that it, four?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "No, because one is bound to turn out to be an A-hole.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Don't you?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Boy, I don't know if I would want to catapult put them into that world.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "-- produce a whole breeding ground of young comedians and comediennes?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Yes, you definitely reach a point -- and I know that through my 20s, it was really about what I was experiencing then, just partying, being young.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "I've always been curious, when you're a comedian and you're high profile and you're out there and you're facing audiences and stuff, how easy is it to use comedy as a mask of how you're really feeling in situations like that?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "I think it's what we are.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Is that healthy or unhealthy?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "I think right now.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Do you still have days when you just bomb, when it just goes horribly wrong an, when you face that awful moment for any comedian?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Seriously, did you ever get those days anymore?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Subjects?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "I think it's -- I made a choice a few years ago.", "docId": "111129pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "What's the ambition left for you?", "qSentId": 662}]